Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.17 01:39:16
Grey's Anatomy S205 前情提要
[Narrator] Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
你有发球权.
Divorce papers.
如果你签字，我就签 然后坐最早的飞机离开这里.
The ball's in your court. If you sign, I'll be on the first plane out.
今晚愿意和我出去吗?
Would you like to go out with me tonight?
医院同意你可以在四个月后 进行内科理论的补考.
The hospital grants you four months to retake the exam.
如果我第二次还没有通过会怎样?
If I don't pass a second time?
你将再不是这里的医生了
You will no longer be a surgical resident.
你看起来不错.
- You look great. - Thanks.
谢谢.
- Are you OK? - You ready to go?
你还好吗?
- I didn't lie. - You withheld the truth.
Yeah. 可以走了吗?
我没撒谎.
- Had I known you were pregnant... - You broke off with me.
你一直隐藏着真相 我如何能知道你
我清楚的记得是你先提出和我分手的.
Yang医生.
- Dr. Yang! - Cristina!
Cristina
[Addison] It's an extrauterine pregnancy. She's bleeding out.
她是宫外孕 而且大出血
我认为我不该在这里.
- [Ellis] I'm not supposed to be here. - [Richard] No, you're not.
不，你不该.
I don't want someone who doesn't want me,
我不想要一个不要我的人, Meredith,
但是如果有万分之一的机会他可能会要我 我不会离开西雅图的.
but if there's the slightest chance that he does, I'm not leaving Seattle.
疼痛来自于所有不同的形式...
[Meredith] Pain comes in all forms.
我过的很愉快，真的.
I had a good time. Really. Thank you.
谢谢，真是一个美好的夜晚.
It was the perfect evening. Best date ever.
从没有过的约会，从未.
- Whatever. - Izzie.
Izzie.
I especially liked the part where you treated me like crap the entire night.
还有，我最喜欢的部分就是 整个晚上你对待我就像对待废物一样.
真有意思.
- That was fun. - I had a good time.
我过的很愉快.
真的?
- Really? - Yeah.
Yeah.
The small twinge, a bit of soreness, the random pain.
阵痛，轻微疼痛，没有规律的痛,
正常的疼痛每天都伴随着我们...
The normal pains we live with every day.
我该走了.
I gotta go.
你认真的?
Seriously?
真的吗?
有一种疼痛你无法忽视.
Then there's the kind of pain we can't ignore.
真的吗?
Seriously?
一级疼痛真是太棒了. 它能阻挡任何其他的事情..
A level of pain so great that it blocks out everything else.
oh,我都睡着了.
- [George] I'm sleeping. - Oh, shut it.
Oh, 给我闭嘴.
Shut...
让世界的其他部分逐渐凋谢...
Makes the rest of the world fade away.
我不想再谈这个了
- [Meredith] I don't want to talk. - [Derek] Meredith...
Meredith.
You didn't sign the divorce papers. Fine. End of discussion.
你并没有签离婚协议.
很好，我明白了.
- Meredith... - What?
讨论到此结束. Meredith.
干吗?!
Until all we can think about is how much we hurt.
直到我们都能仔细考虑...
到底我们伤了多少...
I usually just say "Meredith" then you yell at me.
每次当我刚刚叫你 "meredith," 的时候，你就开始对我大喊大叫了.
我以前没想过这点.
I haven't thought past that point.
我事实上根本没有任何计划.
I actually didn't have anything planned.
如何来控制我们的疼痛，全由我们自己作主.
- How we manage our pain is up to us. - What is that? Hey. Stop it.
Hey, 别打了!
Seriously? Seriously!
你认真的吗?! 真的吗?
真的吗?
Seriously!
这是一张非常非常小的床.
This is a very small bed.
他是个脑外科医生.
He's a brain surgeon.
I look fantastic. I shaved my legs.
我把腿毛都剃了.
He's a brain surgeon. How can he be so brainless?
他是个脑外科医生.
可是他怎么能如此没大脑呢?
- Hello? Seriously! - Seriously!
Hello? 真的啊.
的确.
- Shh. Sleep. - [Thunder]
Shh.
痛...
Pain.
让我们麻痹，安全度过，拥抱它，忽视它...
- We anesthetize... - [lights pop]
Ride it out, embrace it, ignore it...
对于我们当中的一些人来说 对待疼痛最好的办法就是咬牙挺过去.
And for some of us, the best way to manage pain is to just push through it.
你正在滴水.
- You're dripping. - I'm back.
我回来了.我只是想你明白
I just want to make that clear. I'm ready to work.
我回来了,已经准备好重返工作岗位了.
- Has anyone seen Dr. Shepherd? - His name's on the OR board.
今早有人见过Shepherd医生吗?
他的名字在手术公告栏上. 他应该在这里的什么地方.
- He should be here somewhere. - I'm good. Ready to scrub in.
我很好,已经准备好参加手术了.
- I'm 100% on top of my game. - You just got discharged.
我100%的做好准备冲锋陷阵.
你刚刚出院而已,慢慢来.
- Pace yourself. - I'm paced. I'm paced.
我已经很慢了,很慢.
Rounds, people.
Mm-hmm. 你们过来吧.
怎么回事?
What? You're not talking to me anymore?
你再也不想和我说话了?
OK, what happened last night? What is going on with you?
Okay, 昨晚到底怎么了?
你到底怎么了?
我很好.
I'm fine.
你有什么问题?
- What's your problem? - [Snorts]
没事.
Fine. You know what, Alex? No, I'm not talking to you anymore.
知道吗, alex?
不,我再也不搭理你了.
[Pager beeps]
Ahem. Bailey医生?
Dr. Bailey.
Henry lamott, 42岁 Shepherd医生的病人
Henry Lamott, age 42, is scheduled with Dr. Shepherd for a spinal implant
等待做一个脊椎穿刺 来治疗他的疝气疼痛,
to control the pain of his herniated disk.
对所有的止痛药都过敏.
Is allergic to all pain medication...
那个是...
- Is that? - Porn.
毛片.
Porn?
毛片?
- As in porn? - All right.
你的意思是."毛片"?
- What are we watching? - Karev. Go stand in the hall.
完全正确.
我们在看什么?
Karev,走廊站着去.
Uh, Lamott先生和太太 我知道你们是很好的人,
Mr. And Mrs. Lamott, I'm sure you are really nice people,
你们在私人病房里做任何个人的事情--
and what you do in the privacy of your own...
你们不能在这里看毛片. 这里是医院
Look, we can't have porn in here. This is a hospital.
这是因为我的疼痛.
It's for my pain. My doc said it releases endorphins in the brain
我医生说这个可以让我的大脑释放快感,
这样可以帮助我的疼痛在一个可控制的范围内.
and helps keep my pain at a manageable level.
真的?
- Really? - George. Hall.
george--走廊去.
Yeah.
[TV; woman moans]
这是什么?
- What is this? - Nasty, Naughty Nurses... 4.
"淫荡俏护士..."
um, "4个."
[TV; women giggle]
那个看起来一点也不舒服.
- That does not look comfortable. - Trust me. It's not.
信我的,一点也不.
都给我走廊站着去.
Get in the hall.
[& Psaap: Crazy in the Rocket]
nobody knows where they might end up
nobody knows
Oh, oh suppose you'll never know
o'malley, karev,你俩今天去负责缝合.
[Bailey] O'Malley, Karev, you're in the Pit.
Stevens,有个心脏病患者 等着你去处理
Stevens, there's a cardiac patient for you on two.
Yang,留下来观察lamotts.
Yang, keep an eye on the Lamotts. I don't want any problems. Go.
我不想出任何问题,去吧.
Grey, 你妈今晚就出院了.
Grey, your mother's being discharged this evening.
你有安排了, 需要更多时间吗?
- You've made arrangements? - The nursing home is coming at eight.
疗养院的人8点过来.
那好.那么你今天要跟shepherd医生 -derek shepherd.
Then you're with Shepherd, Derek Shepherd, today.
hey,生命短暂,人生苦难.
Hey, life is short. Times are hard.
一路上艰难险阻层出不穷.
The road is long with many a winding turn.
他要你过去的,那你就过去吧.
He asked for you. Take it up with him.
Okay.
OK.
Pete willoughby,25岁 胸部枪伤.
Pete Willoughby, 25-year-old, GSW to the chest.
已经立刻输了860CC血...
- Return of 860 cc's of blood... - Oh, damn, this hurts.
oh,伙计,伤的真重.
He's put out more than 200 cc's over the past hour.
他在一个小时之内又流失了200CC多的血.
没人告诉你电影里那些枪伤到底有多疼.
Movies never say how much it hurts to get shot.
2毫克的吗啡. Alex, 这是我的病人.
Push morphine, two milligrams. Alex, this is my case.
5毫克的吗啡.
Morphine, five milligrams.
你甚至没下指令.
- You didn't call him. - I was here first.
我不用下指令.
You got her first because I let you. Where's the chest films?
我是第一个来的.
你第一个来是因为我让你的
胸片在哪里?
I got it. You always get the surgery. Today, I'm getting a surgery.
Unh.我来吧.
你总是参加手术. 今天,轮到我了.
你俩,有完没完.
Guys. Knock it off. He's one of Seattle's finest.
他是西雅图的警察.
You've got an entire police force watching you.
你俩让整个的警察队伍都在看着呢
传呼Burke医生.
[George] Page Dr. Burke.
告诉他我这里有一个枪伤
- Let him know I'm bringing up a GSW. - "We" are bringing up a GSW.
看起来你今天能回家了ellis.
Looks like you'll be able to go home today, Ellis.
但是我还有病人要看.
- But I still have patients to see. - No. No more patients.
不,没有病人了
我过一会回来对你检查, okay?
I'll be back to check on you later, OK?
你应该知道我正在考虑离开cher.
You should know I'm thinking of leaving Thatcher.
我根本就不该和他结婚.
I should never have married him.
我要离开他,你离开adele.
I'll leave him. You leave Adele.
然后当我们的实习期结束的时候,
Then when our residency's over we can both get jobs at the same hospital.
我们可以在同一家医院找到工作
护士你能去准备一下她出院需要的药吗?
Why don't you get her meds ready for discharge, nurse? Thank you.
谢谢.
[Woman on PA]
[Distant siren]
Ellis...
Ellis, that was a long time ago, remember?
那是很久很久以前的事情了,记得吗?
我们在21年之前就讨论过这个.
We had this discussion 21 years ago.
考虑考虑吧, richard.
Think about it. We should make the break now.
我们应该现在就做
If we wait till residency's over, you'll be at one hospital, I'll be in another.
如果真等我们实习期结束 你会在一个医院里
而我在另外一间医院了.
We could end up at opposite ends of the country. It'll be too late.
最后我们可能会相隔十万八千里. 那时候就什么都晚了
[Bell dings]
meredith.
- Meredith. - Your wife is looking for you.
你老婆正到处找你呢.
Oh, my God, this is hard for me, Meredith.
Oh, 天.
这个对我来说很难, meredith.
Let me make it easy. I'm not going to be that woman.
那好,我来把它简单化
我不会是那种女人...
The one who breaks up a marriage or begs you to want me.
破坏你的婚姻 或者求你和我在一起.
你可以签字离婚,也可以不签 你自己的选择
You can sign the papers or you can not. The choice is yours.
当其中任何一个决定影响我们的关系时 我退出
Either way, when it comes to this relationship, I'm out.
现在,你要我来帮助你的那个病人在哪里?
Now, where's this patient I'm supposed to be helping you with?
那边.
Down there.
你不应该带着狗狗在雨中散步.
You shouldn't have walked the dog in the rain.
Oh, lou, 和雨没有关系 我只不过昏倒了一下.
Oh, Lou, it wasn't the rain. I just passed out.
事实上, Bradley太太--
- Actually, Mrs. Bradley... - Verna.
verna.
Verna. You presented with lateral ST elevations
Verna, 你的症状显示你的血小板很高 以及非常差的相反一致性改变并发心急梗塞
and reciprocal inferior changes consistent with an MI.
也就是说,心脏病发作.
- A heart attack. - [Lou] Oh, my God.
oh, 天.
Lou, don't worry.
Lou, 别担心
I've had little chest pains before and it turned out to be nothing.
我之前也有过这样的胸部小疼痛 后来也没什么事了.
没事的.
This is nothing.
Lou, 别在医生面前.
Lou, not in front of the doctor.
我后背的阵痛持续了一段时间了
[Woman] I've had a twinge in my back for a while.
我以为马上就会消失的 但是昨晚,我的腿失去知觉了,
I thought it would go away, but then last night, my legs went numb.
然后今天早上,我的后背--
This morning, my back... The pain is just too much.
太疼了.
Chue小姐,我会帮你按上一个P.C.A.仪器, (疼痛渗透控制仪)
Miss Chue, we'll put you on a PCA pump, give you morphine to control the pain.
我会给你一些吗啡, 这个能帮你控制住疼痛.
谢谢.
- Thank you. - OK. But there's a greater problem.
但是有个更大的问题.
- I've just looked at your MRI... - Anna!
我刚刚看了你的磁共振成像.--
Anna...
为什么你来之前没给我们打电话?
- Why didn't you call us before coming? - I'm sorry. These are my parents.
对不起.
这是我父母.
Hi.
- Hi. - What's going on?
怎么回事?
Anna's MRI has shown that she has a myxopapillary ependymoma.
我刚刚想解释一下anna的磁共振成像.
显示她有一个室鼓膜瘤--
是在脊椎槽道里面的肿瘤,
It's a tumor in her spinal canal.
好消息是,我们可以做手术取出.
But the good news is that we can operate.
你有95%的机会可以完全康复 如果我们尽快准备手术的话.
You have a 95% chance of fully recovering
if we get you to surgery as soon as possible.
一刻也不能再等了
We can't wait. With a tumor this aggressive
这个肿瘤的侵略性相当快,
even waiting another day puts you at risk for permanent paralysis.
即使只是晚一天手术的话 你都会有终身瘫痪的危险
爹?
Father?
不
No. No surgery.
绝不手术
Mr. Chue, without surgery, Anna will be paralyzed within the next 24 hours.
Chue先生,如果不手术的话,
anna很可能在未来24小时内瘫痪.
今天绝不手术
No surgery today. We're taking her home.
我们带她回家.
- Anna needs surgery. - She can have it another time.
Anna需要手术
那她可以其他时间再做
- Mr. Chue... - We are taking our daughter home.
Chue先生--
我们要把女儿带回家
Anna, 你已经过18岁了
Anna, you're over 18. You don't need your father's consent.
你不需要你父亲的同意
我是hmong信徒,我父亲是长者
I'm Hmong, and my father is the elder.
如果他让我回家,我就回家
If he says I go home, I go home.
Hmong? 找找什么意思.
Hmong? Let's find out what that means.
Okay.联络社工.
Contact Social Services, see if we can get somebody to talk to them.
看看我们是否能找个人下来和他谈谈.
我还需要继续处理她出院的要求吗?
- Do I process her discharge? - Yeah. It's insane, but we have to.
Yeah,我们必须这么做,虽然太愚蠢了, 我们还是需要这么做
It reminds me of a case I had in New York where a woman...
这个病例让我想起来我在纽约的时候 有一次这个女人来我的办公室--
你还需要我做什么和工作有关的吗?
Look, do you need me for anything else work-related?
听着,我结婚11年了
Look. I was married for 11 years. Addison is my family.
Addison是我的家人. 那是11个感恩节,11个生日,11个圣诞节,
That is 11 Thanksgivings, 11 birthdays, and 11 Christmases.
然后有一天,我要来签字 来结束我的家人?
In one day, I'm supposed to sign a piece of paper and end my family?
一个正常的人不会这么做的- 不会一点都不犹豫.
A person doesn't do that. Not without hesitation.
我有权利有一点点的不确定.
I'm entitled to a little uncertainty. A moment to understand the magnitude
只是需要一点时间来弄明白 从我生命中夺走一个人到底对我意味着什么.
of what it means to cut somebody out of my life.
我有权至少有那么一分钟,痛苦的怀疑
- I'm entitled to at least one moment... - [door opens]
...of painful doubt.
如果你能有那么一点点谅解的话,一定很好.
And a little understanding from you would be nice.
Shepherd医生,还没走呢,我明白了.
- Dr. Shepherd. Still here, I see. - I couldn't leave you.
我不能离开你们.
- Have you seen the other Dr. Shepherd? - I'll tell him you're looking for him.
见过Shepherd医生吗?
我会转告他你在找他
那个,谢谢,就是,陪着我.
- So, thanks for, you know, being there. - No thanks needed.
不需要感谢
- OK. - So where are we?
Okay.
我们说到哪里了? (Yang理解为字面意思:我们在哪里)
The north-east corner of a hospital.
Uh, 医院的东北角.
Oh, 我可以回来工作了.
- Oh, I'm getting back on my feet. - Fine.
很好.
- That doesn't mean that... - Cristina...
但是并不意味着... --cristina.
- It's my first day back, I've got... - I'm not waiting forever.
这是我第一天回来工作.
我不会一直等下去的.
[Elevator bell]
Hey, karev 和 o'malley带来一个G.S.W.
Karev and O'Malley are bringing a GSW. Want to scrub in?
想加入吗?
No can do. I'm trying to get out of here at a decent hour tonight.
不去,不做额外工作 我在试图今晚可以准时下班.
怎么,你有约会?
- What, you got a date? - Yes. Yes, I do.
是啊是啊,我有
A handsome man is whisking me away to a love nest for the weekend.
一个帅小伙正在爱巢 向我招手邀请我一起过周末呢
你是在执勤的时候被击中的吗?
You got shot in the line of duty?
工作的第一个月.
First month on the job. Can you believe my luck?
能相信我的运气吗?
Guy pulls a gun and I freeze up.
那边一扣扳机,我就失去知觉了
新手自己吃枪子儿.
The rookie who let himself get shot.
我永远不会忘记这个的
- I'm never gonna live this down. - Sure, you will.
我肯定你会记着
You think?
你这么认为?
绝对
Absolutely.
[Elevator bell]
Hey,  我把verna bradley的测试拿回来了.
Hey, I got Verna Bradley's tests back.
我不认为她有心脏病
I don't think she had a heart attack.
Yeah, 但是看看她心电图上的变化 她一定有点什么.
Look at the changes in her EKG. She had something.
Yeah,但是她的连续s和 心肌压力回波结果,都显示正常.
Her serial enzymes and dobutamine stress echo were negative.
我觉得她没事
- I actually think she's fine. - Get a cardiac cath. Be thorough.
在心脏插入一个导管看看.
Izzie, 认真点.
我很认真了.
I am thorough.
那么伙计,izzie到底怎么了?
- [Alex] What's the deal with lzzie? - She shaved her legs for you.
她为了你腿毛都剃了
还有你甚至没亲她一下说晚安.
- And? - You didn't even kiss her good night.
她连腿毛都为你剃了,你竟然没继续下去?
- You didn't follow through? - Hey, I always follow through.
hey,我继续下去了,我一直都是
昨晚你没有.
- You didn't last night. - Mind your own business.
管好你自己的事儿吧
Mind...
管好...
她是有期望的 女人都有期望,而你并没有让她的期望发生.
She had expectations. Women have expectations. And you didn't meet them.
我和这些女人住一起.
I live with these women.
每次你们这些家伙都不满足他们的期待,
When you guys don't meet their expectations, I hear about it.
然后我必须听他们发牢骚,昨晚我根本就没睡.
I didn't get any sleep last night.
现在知道了,这就是我的事儿
So, you know, it is my business.
[Clattering]
[Monitor beeps]
伙计,我们不动了
- Dude, we're not moving. - Really! You think?
真的吗?你觉得?
[Wheezes]
[Woman on PA] Dr. Cole, 2621. Dr. Cole, 2621.
[Lights fizz]
[Groans]
你知道一个术后疤痕需要多久才能愈合吗?
You know how long the surgical scar takes to heal.
你肯定很疼. 你应该吃点止痛的.
You must be in pain. You should take something.
止痛药是给小孩准备的
- Drugs are for babies. - I hate Alex.
我讨厌alex.
- And the non sequitur award goes to... - I'm sorry. I hate Alex.
那么这个毫无根据奖的得主是...
对不起
我讨厌 alex.
我和 derek分手了.
- I broke up with Derek. - Burke wants to have a relationship.
Burke想要拍拖.
Boys are stupid.
男人都是傻瓜.
[Woman on PA]
Yep.
"如果电梯停了,千万不要惊慌."
[George] "If elevator should stop, do not become alarmed."
"按警报按钮来通知外界救援."
"Press the button marked 'alarm' for assistance."
如果他们不想让我们惊慌
If they don't want us to be alarmed,
那为什么这个按钮叫"警报"呢?
- why call the button "alarm"? - That didn't work the last five times.
你按了5次根本都不工作. 用你的大脑想想.
我们没办法了,只能呆在这里.
- We've lost power. We're stuck. - [Pete groans]
Oh.
You OK?
你没事吧?
His pressure is falling.
他的血压正在下降.
Alex, there's a lot more of his blood in the Pleurovac.
Alex,他的胸腔里流了更多的血. 我们要尽快带他去手术室.
- We need to get him to the OR. - OK. Don't whisper.
Okay, 你正在说悄悄话.
I don't want to complain, but I got a bullet in my chest
别偷偷摸摸的.
我是说,我并不想在这里抱怨,
但是我胸腔里有颗子弹
and whispering isn't a sign that I'm going to be A-OK, you know?
而悄悄话并不表示我很快就没事了,明白吗?
该死,这个坏了
- Damn it. It's out. - It's bad. It's bad, right?
很糟糕,很糟糕,对吗?
总有人会把我们弄出去的,别担心
Someone is going to get us out of here. Don't worry.
怎么样了?
- How we doing? - Can you move me to another room?
Oh, 能给我换个房间吗?
- The lights and TV went out. - Power outage in the east wing.
灯和电视都停了.
东翼的电力供应不足. 他们正在抢修,马上就好了.
They'll have it back on soon.
你不是紧急病人. 你在这里没事的.
- You're not critical. You'll be fine. - Oh, God! What am I gonna do?
Oh, 天,那我还能做点什么?
- You mean... - Without my porn.
你是说...
没了毛片?
看书,或者和你老婆交交心
Read a book. Talk to your wife.
不,因为暴风雨来了,学校提早放学.
School closed early because of the storm.
她去接孩子了
She had to pick up the kids. She won't be back until after dinner.
晚饭之后她才能回来
我相信你一定会找到一些正常的办法来娱乐自己的.
Well, I'm sure you can find some normal way of amusing yourself.
我需要毛片!
- I need my porn! - Yeah.
Yeah.
[Addison] Lightning hit a substation.
闪电袭击了一个变电站. 我们正在用备用发电机.
We're running on backup generators. One of them is down. Richard, breathe.
其中一个不工作了.
Richard, 放松
The only means of transporting patients from the ER to the OR isn't working.
唯一的办法把病人从急诊室 送到手术室,但是并不奏效.
别告诉我放松
Don't tell me to breathe. I'll breathe if I want to breathe.
我会在我需要的时候放松
电梯在两层之间
- [Man] Caught between floors. - How bad is it?
有多糟糕?
- Two interns and a GSW to the chest. - Good air in, bad air out.
两个实习生和一个胸部枪伤患者.
好的进,坏的出.
加油啊大家,把这个门打开
Come on, people, get those doors open.
这里有东西档着,再也打不开了.
- [Man] It's jammed. It won't open. - [Bailey] Move.
好吧,移动,移动 电梯门和走向一样宽
- This is as wide as it goes. - What... What did you two do?
你俩做什么?
什么都没有做!
Nothing.
病人怎么样?
- How's the patient? - He's not looking so good.
他看起来并不好.
[Thunder]
[Lights fizz]
灯为什么一直在闪?
- Why do the lights keep flickering? - Something about a backup generator.
因为备用发电机.
这个机器会给你提供一个持续的吗啡注射,
This pump will provide you with a morphine drip and should stop your pain.
这会停止你的疼痛.
I told you, I don't need it. I'm going home.
我,我告诉你了,我不需要这个,我要回家
你需要签署一个AMA表格 表示你回家是完全不听医生的劝告.
You'll have to sign a form stating that you're leaving against medical advice.
好
Fine.
我了解这个从没有过,而且困扰你
I know this is new and confusing.
我已经叫了社工了 她马上过来会和你聊聊
I called a social worker and she's willing to talk to you...
别介意啊,你们鬼妹的文化就是分崩离析爱.
Spare me the white-girl, cultural-divide love.
我就在离这里不远的那条街长大 我在一个乐队里演奏
I grew up down the street. I play in a band. I went to U-Dub.
我去u-dub. 我成功了.
I get it. But my father doesn't.
但是我爸爸没有.
他说不,那就是不.
He says no, it's no.
我们正在讨论的是你是否还可以再行走.
We're talking about your ability to ever walk again.
那是你在说的,. 我在说的是我的家庭.
That's what you're talking about. I'm talking about my family.
你有曾经听过hmong人吗?
Have you even heard of the Hmong people?
我们的宗教有规定,那是一个老去的方式
Our religion has got rules that are way old
那方式坚如磐石,很强的精神效力 不容许你有半点马虎.
and way set in stone and way spiritual and you don't mess with them.
你不会对你的祖先发火...
You don't anger the ancestors.
即使如果你在舌头上穿洞,还玩乐队.
Even if you pierce your tongue and play in a band.
那规定到底是什么?
What are the rules, exactly?
所有的深切治疗室的患者搬去南翼.
ICU patients are going to the south wing.
其他控制住病情和减缓恶化的病人去北翼.
Telemetry and stepdown patients, north wing.
你呼我了
- You paged me. - Porn as pain management?
毛片来治疗疼痛?
You met Henry. There are lots of theories on how to treat pain.
你见过henry了.
Yeah, 太多不同的理论方法来治疗疼痛.
而你用毛片来治疗他的疼痛?
Porn as pain management?
听着, 可能是那种毛片, 像艺术和音乐一样的(三级片?),
It's possible pornography can stimulate the brain
能够刺激大脑分泌快感,以至于使疼痛最小化.
to produce endorphins that minimize pain.
毛片疼痛治疗法.
- Porn as pain management. - I didn't prescribe it. It wasn't me.
我并没有开那个处方,那不是我.
Take it up with the physician.
和主治医生去理论吧.
If he turns out to be some sex weirdo, it's on you. That's all I'm saying.
如果那男人产生任何其他的 异常性行为,都是你的责任.
这正是我要说的.
- Oh, and your wife is looking for you. - I know.
Oh, 你老婆正在找你呢
我知道.
- Derek. - Yes?
Derek.
Talk to Anna's father. I'd do it myself but having testicles is a requirement.
Yes.
你需要和anna的父亲谈谈.
我已经做了,但是我猜 最好是找个带种的来和他谈.
社工怎么了?
- What happened to Social Services? - According to Anna, they can't help us.
按照anna说法,他们根本帮不了什么.
Anna's father believes she's missing something she needs for surgery.
很显然,anna的父亲认为 手术会导致她失去一些东西.
失去一些东西?什么?
- Missing something? Missing what? - One of her souls.
她的一个灵魂.
我们不需要社工了,我们需要一个巫师.
We don't need a social worker. We need a shaman.
巫师?
Shaman?
Cardio告诉我你的心脏导管插入干的不错.
Cardio tells me your cath went just fine.
那些擦伤是正常的吗?
- Is that much bruising normal? - Your wound looks good.
Bradley太太,你的伤口看起来没事,
So do the results on your cath. You have no blockages in your arteries.
心脏导管插入的结果也没事.
你没有动脉血塞.
- Which means? - You did not have a heart attack.
你的意思是?
你绝对没有心脏病
[Both chuckle]
那么我能回家了?
- So I can go home? - Not yet.
还没.
Your EKG shows significant changes.
你的心电图有很大的变化,
我要在你出院之前找到原因.
And I'm going to find out why before you leave the hospital.
Hey, pete,你干吗呢?
- Hey, Pete, what are you doing? - I have to get home.
我要回家.
- Pete, you're in the hospital. - Need to get home. Need to get home.
Pete, 你在医院呢.
我要回家
我必须回家
- What's his blood pressure? - It's not reading. He's too agitated.
他血压如何?
读不出来,他太激动了.
- How's his pulse? - Thready, but still there.
脉搏呢?
像线一样,不过至少还有
- Do you have instruments? - A code box and gloves.
你们那边有什么工具吗?
只有密码箱和几副手套.
You didn't bring an open chest tray?
你们没带个开胸盘?
- We thought... - No time for excuses.
没有,我们以为--
- Blood pressure. - I've taken it three times.
你没时间找借口.O'malley,血压.
我已经测了3次了.
- And? - I can't hear a systolic over 50.
然后呢?
我听不到50次以上的心跳.
他快要挂了.
He's gonna die.
[Pete groans]
插喉,我马上回来.
- Intubate him. I'll be back. - Where are you going?
等等,你去哪里?
To get an instrument tray. You guys are going to have to open up his chest.
去拿一件开胸的工具.
你们要把他的胸腔打开
[Pete groans]
你确定吗?
- Are you sure about that? - No.
不.
burke什么时候回来?
When's Burke coming back?
[Distant thunder]
Burke医生什么时候回来?
When is Dr. Burke coming back?
Alex?
- Alex... - Oh, would you shut up?
Oh,你能闭嘴吗?
[Thunder]
Chue先生...
Mr. Chue. You want to take Anna home for a healing ritual?
你要把anna带回家做个治疗法事?
When sickness comes, it means that one of our souls is missing.
当疾病降临的时候, 那意味着我们其中的一个灵魂正在丢失.
Anna需要在手术前,找回她完整的灵魂.
Anna needs to have her souls intact before surgery.
她需要个巫师.
- She needs a shaman. - Well, you could have told me that.
你可以告诉我这个.
Why? So you could call me a fool?
为什么? 那样你就可以把我看成傻瓜了?
我尊重你的传统 尽管我不理解
I respect that you have traditions that I can't understand.
但是你穿着这身3000美元的西装,
But you're standing beside me in a $3,000 suit
我相信你同时也尊重我告诉你的事实
so I know you respect that I'm telling you
Anna如果想要继续行走的话, 她需要在未来的24小时内尽快手术
Anna needs surgery in the next 24 hours if she's going to continue to walk.
她不能离开医院.
She can't leave this hospital.
她不能在没有灵魂的情况下手术,她会死的.
She can't undergo surgery without her soul. She'd die.
那么好吧
All right then.
我们就找来一个巫师吧,今天,就在医院里.
We're just gonna have to get a shaman. Today. In the hospital.
巫师并没有在电话薄上登记.
Shamans aren't in the Yellow Pages.
我们的巫师离这里有50英里.
Our shaman is 500 miles from here. You are an arrogant man.
你真是个自大狂.
No. I'm just a guy with access to a helicopter.
不,我仅仅是个有权使用直升飞机的人罢了
谢谢
Thank you.
找到她的灵魂并不容易.
- Finding her soul won't be easy. - It never is.
决不.
这太不合理了.
[Richard] This is unconscionable. Not enough power to move those elevators?
难道没有足够电力来移动电梯吗?
They're replacing the backup. Fire department is standing by.
他们正在努力取代备用发电机.
消防队随时准备
- Critical patients? - Moved to south wing.
所有的重病患者呢?
- Incoming trauma? - Rerouted to Mercy West.
搬到南翼去了.
外伤患者呢?
都送去 mercy west医院了.
- That backup should have been replaced. - Yes, sir.
备用发电机应该去年就换了.
是的,先生
- Why didn't it happen? - Chief, you'd have to ask maintenance.
为什么没有?
头儿,你应该去问维修部.
我不想知道
- I wouldn't know. - Dr. Bailey, you know everything.
Bailey医生,
你知道所有的事情
Tell me whose butt to kick.
告诉我谁应该开除.
那应该是你,头儿
That would be your butt, Chief.
你没有批准发电机的更新, 省钱要买一个新的磁共振成像仪.
You didn't authorize the replacement generator,
saving money for the new MRI machine.
Um... 我需要回去处理..手术室
Um...
I need to get on back down to the... OR.
[Monitor beeps]
Hey.
Hey, this isn't gonna be too sterile, but we can still try.
这个不可能太危险了,
但是我们还是要试试.
Prep and drape the patient.
准备病人开胸.
[Thunder]
Hey, 能给我 verna bradley所有的病历吗?
Can you get me copies of all Verna Bradley's records and page me?
然后呼我,我会在手术室那层
- I'll be on the OR floor. - [PA] Dr. Bennett...
hey, 哪里, um,
Hey! Wait... Where are you two going so fast?
hey, 你们俩这么急着去哪里啊?
Burke is talking George and Alex through heart surgery in the elevator.
Burke正在教george和alex如何在电梯里做心脏手术.
Shepherd在准备一个巫师手术前法事.
Shepherd's setting up a shaman healing ritual.
动起来啊.
Rock on.
我还有个毛片大王呢.
I have porn guy.
救命啊.
[Mr. Lamott] Help! Please!
Lamott先生,怎么了?
Mr. Lamott? What's wrong?
你的血压提高了
Your pressure's elevated.
脉搏很快.
Pulse is racing. You're really in pain.
这次你可是真的疼了哦.
What? Do you think?
那你想什么呢?
Are you telling me the porn actually sedated you?
你是要告诉我,那毛片的确让你镇静下来吗?
你想什么呢?我是那种变态
You think I'm a pervert, watching that stuff in front of you?
在你面前看毛片?
Well... yes.
是啊
OK, OK.
Oh, okay. Okay.
[Sighs] You're allergic to most narcotics and NSAIDs.
你对大部分的止痛剂过敏
我猜,我们可以试试droperidol和diphenhydramine.
I suppose we can try droperidol and diphenhydramine.
去年这些让我昏迷了.
That put me into a coma last year.
那我去找一个麻醉师来吧.
Well, I can get an anesthesiologist down here.
Oh, 不行,你明天就手术了
But with your surgery tomorrow, he won't give you an epidural block.
我觉得他不会给你个局部麻醉.
- What am I gonna do? - Uh... hold on.
那我怎么办啊?
Uh, 等一下.
我们真要这么做啊?
We're really gonna do this.
接着.
Take these.
Karev, 接着手术刀.
Karev, take the scalpel.
Alex,快点
Alex! Come on.
Alex.
Alex!
鼓风.
Ventilate!
我来.
[George] I got it.
现在我做什么
What do I do?
Make a large, anterior, lateral, midaxillary incision
在腋中前面偏一点的位置 尽量大的切开直至第五条动脉间的空隙.
in the fifth intercostal space.
多大?
- How... How large? - [Burke] As long as possible.
尽量大.你需要两只手都能伸进去.
You need to get two hands in there. It needs to be long and deep.
要够长够深
- Use the scissors if you have to. - OK.
如果有需要,可以用剪刀
Okay.
但是要小心别切到肺或者心脏.
- Don't cut into the lung or heart. - How can I be sure of that?
我们如何小心这个?
You just have to be sure.
你就需要小心就对了.
我们不是在堪撒斯了.
We're not in Kansas any more.
你的巫师迟到了
Your shaman's late.
我们的巫师从来不迟到.
My shaman is never late.
你们能看到什么吗?
Can you see anything? Poor George, he doesn't have the steadiest hands.
可怜的george. 他胳膊一直在颤抖.
Izzie. Yeah.
- Izzie. - Yeah?
他能听到你
He can hear you.
o'malley...下面怎么样了?
O'Malley? How you doing down there?
The fire department's here.
消防队的人来了,他们能打开门.
- They can get the doors open... - No.
不,谁也别动 谁也别动电梯
Nobody works on the elevator.
我有一个正在开胸并且非常紧张的实习生在那里.
I have an open chest and a very nervous intern in there. Keep them back.
没有我的命令不要让他们过来
- OK, guys, we're not going... - O'Malley?
Okay,  你们,我们不要....
o'malley...
我没有切到心脏或者肺.
Dr. Burke, I didn't cut the heart or the lungs.
Burke医生,我没有切到心脏或者肺.
Good, good, O'Malley. Really good.
Okay, 很好
好o'malley. 非常好.
Now, check for injuries and do a pericardiotomy.
现在检查伤口,然后做心包切开术.
我需要一些包垫,镊子,以及夹钳.
I'll need some lap pads, forceps, Metzenbaums and Satinsky clamps?
遵命.
Yes, you will.
你要是告诉其他人我为你做了这个,
You tell anyone I did this for you,
不仅我会杀了你, 我还会把你尸体切成小块换钱花.
not only will I kill you, I will sell your body parts for cash.
Okay. 那么....那些女人们
OK. So...
There were these women. Nurses.
护士,3个护士
Three nurses. And they were... naughty.
他们正在...淘气
他们非常非常淘气
They were really, really naughty. They were three naughty nurses. Saucy, even.
他们是三个淘气俏护士
很漂亮--他们又漂亮,又不乖,又调皮.
They were saucy and bad and naughty. Three saucy, bad, naughty nurses.
三个漂亮的调皮小护士--
They were taking a shower. Together.
他们在谈论洗澡.
在给彼此擦浴液,
Soaping each other up. And then this doctor walks in
就在这个时候,医生进来了,
他看到了那3个调皮的小护士
and he sees these three naughty, bad nurses
和她们那很大的...
with these great big...
Bradley太太, 你有意识到在过去的7年中 在这同一天里你都会住进医院吗?
Mrs. Bradley, do you realize that you've been admitted to the hospital
on this date for the past seven years?
Oh,不可能
That can't be.
我不确定具体的日子,但是--
- I don't remember the date exactly... - I have the medical records.
我有医疗记录.
On this date for the past seven years you have what looks like a heart attack.
在过去7年的同一天里, 你一直都像心脏病发作一样.
不,不,我知道我有一些害怕 但是我没有--
No. No, I know I've had some scares but I don't...
每年的今天吗?
Every year on this date?
这一天对你个人来说有什么特别的意义吗?
Is there significance to this date for you?
没有
No. Nothing.
第一年你在做什么,
What were you doing the first time you had a cardiac episode?
你第一次有心脏病的时候?
Who can remember back that far?
Oh,谁能记着那么久的事情啊?
我们在院子里 我能记着,因为我们的邻居--
We were in the yard. I remember because our neighbor... What was his name?
他叫什么?
- Ted. - That's right. He died.
Ted.
对,我想他死于动脉瘤.
Of an aneurysm, I think.
我们看着殡仪馆的人把他抬走,
And we watched as the funeral home people took him away
之后你就第一次发作心脏病了
and you had your first attack.
你和ted很亲近吗?
- And you were close to Ted? - No. We barely knew Ted.
不. Oh, 我们对ted了解很少.
那让人很难过 但是这和verna心脏有什么关系呢?
That was all very sad, but what does that have to do with Verna's heart?
我从心包膜中取出了一个小血块.
I removed a small clot from the pericardium.
没有显著的心脏损伤.
- No obvious cardiac injuries. - Change in the vitals?
情况有改变吗?
- BP's still too low to register. - We need to cross-clamp the aorta.
B.P.还是很低,无法显示
我们需要交叉夹住大动脉.
一直夹着,直到你能感觉到 两个管状结构再松开
Stick your hand in and bluntly dissect down
until you feel two tube-like structures.
食道应该在中间偏前的位置.
The esophagus will be more medial and anterior.
Um,我能感觉到一个血管像衣领一样,
I feel one tube that's easily collapsible
另外一个,更多肌肉,很柔软
and the other's more muscular, spongy.
我能感觉到脊骨就在下面
I feel... I can feel the spine just underneath it.
对,你正在触摸大动脉.
- Yes! You're touching the aorta. - I'm touching the aorta.
我在触摸大动脉.
Wrap the index finger of your left hand around it
绕着你左手的食指缠上 然后用你的右手拿着夹钳.
and apply the Satinsky clamp with your right hand.
搞定了.
Got it. Wait, I... I think I can localize the bleeding.
等下,我想我能止住流血
我想流血来自于次级腔动脉.
It's coming from the inferior vena cava.
能找到伤口吗?
- Can you find the lesion? - Yeah. Yeah, I think I can feel it.
Yeah.
Yeah, 我想我能感觉到.
处理起来有点远.
- It's too far in to repair. - How big is it?
有多大?
Small, maybe... smaller than a dime.
很小,可能比一个一角硬币还小.
Okay, o'malley, 我要你把你的手指插到那个洞里面.
OK, O'Malley. I want you to take your finger and plug the hole.
我能感觉到他的心脏开始填满了.
I can feel his heart starting to fill more. It's beating a little stronger.
跳动比以前强一些了.
- Excellent. Keep your finger there. - OK. Now what?
好极了.
你手指继续留在那边.
Okay. 现在怎么办?
就这些.
- That's it. - That's it?
就这些?
我就这么站着,手指插在洞里?
[George] I just stand here with my finger plugging the hole?
直到我们把你们弄出来,送到手术室为止
Until we can get you out of that elevator and into the OR.
Bailey医生,
Bailey, you can tell the firemen to get my guys out of there.
你可以让消防员过来把我的人弄出来了
Will do. OK. We're ready.
马上就去.
Okay,我们准备好了
O'malley.
- O'Malley. - Yes, sir?
是的先生.
You just flew solo.
你刚刚干的很漂亮.
谢谢先生.
Thank you, sir.
Okay, anna,我们现在要关掉PCA机器了,
OK, Anna, we're going to shut off the PCA pump now,
这意味着你会感觉很痛--
which means you'll be in a lot of pain for the duration of...
在治疗法事期间.
- The healing ritual. - Are you OK with that?
你对这个没问题吧?
Yeah. They can't find my soul if I'm medicated.
是的,如果我在用药的话,我就找不到我的灵魂了.
没有痛苦没有收获,对吗?
- No pain, no gain, right? - It's not just for your father.
这不仅仅是为了你父亲.
You believe it too, right?
你也相信这个,对吗?
I know it sounds like a load of crap but watch the ritual. You'll see.
我知道这听起来很不可思议,
但是看看法事,你们就会明白了.
看什么?
- See what? - The moment it happens.
出现的那一刻.
[& Mike Doughty: I Hear The Bells]
我准备好了.
I'm ready.
Oh, yes, 我是这么这么淘气的
"Oh, yes! I'm so very, very naughty,"
bianca 说就像她一样,把听诊器掉了.
Bianca said as she dropped her stethoscope.
"我也是," crystal说
"Me too!" said Crystal as she snapped on her surgical glove.
然后她大力的吮吸她的医用手套
然后还有marta...
And then there was Marta...
我说到哪儿了?
- Where was I? - Marta.
Marta.
Oh, yes. Marta was the naughtiest nurse of all because she knew how...
Oh, yes. marta是他们中最淘气的护士了 因为她知道如何--
[TV; woman giggles]
oh, 谢天谢地
- Oh, thank God. - [Man] We're back up.
回来了.
你认为找回一个迷失的灵魂需要多久?
How long do you think it takes to retrieve a lost soul?
我不知道
I don't know.
准备走了, george.
- Way to go, George. - I have my finger in a heart.
我手指还在他的心脏里呢.
Very cool.
太酷了.
[& Way Out West: Don't Forget Me]
你有压力心肌炎.
- You have stress cardiomyopathy. - Cardiomyopathy?
心肌炎?能告诉我那是什么吗
- What... Can you tell me what that is? - It's Ted.
是ted.
Ted?
Ted.
Ted. Not just the neighbor you barely knew, was he?
他不仅仅是一个你几乎不认识的邻居,对吗?
不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
因为每年在他死的那天,
Every year, on the day he died, you get a rush of adrenaline caused by stress.
你的肾上腺素都会因 压力而急剧增加.
你的血压上升,胸口疼痛...
Your pressure rises, you have chest pains... and you end up here.
最后你来医院.
27 年了...
27 years.
我爱那个隔壁的男人,他也爱我.
I loved the man next door, and he loved me.
我知道这个听起来像什么...
I know how this is gonna sound but... Ted was my soul mate.
ted是我的灵魂伴侣.
然后,他就死了.
And then he just died.
真难过.
It's grief.
你的心脏停止,是因为为ted哀悼
Your heart stops because you're grieving for Ted.
那么...
[Sniffs] So... what do I do next?
我下面应该做什么
I mean, how do you treat it?
你如何治疗我?
真希望我知道.
I wish I knew.
我告诉thatch了,我要离开他.
I told Thatch I'm leaving him.
你已经离开thatcher了, ellis.
You left Thatcher, Ellis, but I couldn't bring myself to leave Adele.
但是我没办法离开adele.
记得吗?
Do you remember?
马的画...
Painted horses.
yes.
Yes. We were on the carousel in the park. It was raining.
我们在一个公园里的喧闹的酒会上. 下起了雨
波士顿军区给了我一个机会.
- I have an offer from Boston General. - You took it to get away.
因为这个你离开了.
We swore we'd never talk again about what we had together.
我们曾发过誓我们永远也不讨论我们曾经一起过.
这应该是我们永远的秘密.
It was gonna always be our secret.
Richard...
Richard?
yes, ellis.
Yes, Ellis?
酒会让我做了那个决定.
Carousels give me the creeps.
你如何容忍这个的?
How do you put up with it?
我是说,"淫荡俏护士, 4"
I mean, Nasty, Naughty Nurses 4 and, I'm assuming, 1, 2 and 3.
我假定1,2,和3?
- He's my Henry. - I know.
他是我的henry.
But don't you find it misogynistic and degrading and kind of...
我知道,但是你没发现 那些歧视女性的可耻行径有点...
一天24小时的毛片? 说真的,这就是你的生活?
[sighs] I mean, 24 hours a day of porn?
Seriously? That's your life?
我感激那个.
I'm grateful for it. It takes away his pain.
那个可以把他的疼痛带走.
See, the thing is, Henry...
还有, 重点是henry--henry也带走了我的疼痛.
Henry takes away my pain.
我撒了谎
I lied.
我不会退出这个复杂关系的.
I'm not out of this relationship, I'm in.
我加入.我肯定加入 真是耻辱,因为我要恳求--
I'm so in, it's humiliating, because here I am begging.
meredith, 请你--
- Meredith... - Shut up.
别说话.
You say Meredith and I yell, remember?
你一说 "meredith,"我就大喊大叫,记得吗?
- Yeah. - OK. Here it is.
Yeah.
Okay...
是这样.
Your choice? It's simple. Her or me.
你的选择非常简单--
要她还是要我？
我知道她也很好.
And I'm sure she's really great... but, Derek, I love you.
但是derek, 我爱你...
非常非常...
In a really, really big, "pretend to like your taste in music,
假装喜欢你喜欢的音乐,
让你吃最后剩下的一块蛋糕,
let you eat the last piece of cheesecake,
在你窗户外面在我头上举着收音机
hold a radio over my head outside your window,"
不幸的方式让我讨厌你
unfortunate way that makes me hate you, love you.
爱你.
So pick me.
所以,选我
Choose me.
要我
爱我
Love me.
我今晚会在joe的酒吧, 所以如果你决定签那份协议...
I'll be at Joe's tonight.
So, if you do decide to sign the papers, meet me there.
来找我吧
[Sighs]
Good-bye, ellis.
Goodbye, Ellis.
我明天去看你.Okay?
I am gonna come see you tomorrow, OK?
他不爱她.
He doesn't love her.
他不能
He can't.
但是无论如何他都要和她在一起.
But he'll stay with her anyway. She's his wife.
她是他的妻子
妈妈?
Mom?
- Mommy. - Meredith.
Meredith...
你长大了.
- You grew up. - I did.
我长大了.
It's a shame. It's awful being a grownup.
Hmm. 真可惜
做一个成年人真没劲.
但是那喧闹的酒会从没有停止过.
But the carousel never stops turning.
你没办法离开
You can't get off.
Okay.
OK.
你觉得他会来?
You think he'll show?
他会.
He'll show.
[& Not Tonight: Tegan $ Sara]
[Bell jangles]
hey.
Hey.
你病人怎么样了?
How's your patient?
把灵魂找回来了?
- The one that got her soul back? - She's going to be fine.
她会没事的.
我要走了.
- Gotta go. - Look at you. You look like a girl.
看看你,你看起来像个女人一样.
- Is that your date? - That's my husband.
是约会吗?
那是我老公.
- You're married? - Ten years today.
你已经结婚了?
今天整整10年
我怎么会不知道你结婚了呢.
- I didn't know you were married. - You never asked.
你从没问过我
你还没签离婚协议书呢,对吗?
You haven't signed those divorce papers yet, have you?
Bailey...告诉我该怎么办.
Bailey. Tell me what to do.
[Chuckles]
天,为什么这个如此艰难?
- God, why does this have to be so hard? - It's not hard.
根本就没什么难的
It's painful but it's not hard.
只是痛苦,但不困难
Come on, you know what to do already.
别闹了,你知道你已经决定了
If you didn't, you wouldn't be in so much pain.
如果你不知道,你不会这么痛苦.
疼痛,你必须挺过来,
[Meredith] Pain. You just have to ride it out.
期待它会自己消失不见,
Hope it goes away on its own.
期待它导致的伤口自动愈合.
Hope the wound that caused it heals.
所以..这里是我们开始的地方.
So here's where we are.
我做了大量工作,竞争激烈,我永远是对的
I work too much, I'm competitive, I'm always right.
我打鼾
- And I snore. - What?
什么?
我正在试呢.
I'm trying here.
Oh... Oh.
Oh!
- Yeah. - So?
那么?
OK, we're a couple.
Okay.我们是一对
Whatever. Don't make a big deal about it.
管它呢,别当成了不起的大事
根本就没有解决方法,没有简单回答.
There are no solutions.
No easy answers.
你只能深呼吸,然后等待它下沉..
You just breathe deep and wait for it to subside.
Oh, man. I just...
- [laughter] - [Bell jangles]
[Sighs] He's not coming.
他不会来了.
你们觉得他不会来了
- You don't think he's coming. - He might come.
他可能会来
Yeah.你永远不知道
- Yeah. You never know. - He's definitely coming.
他肯定会来.
- [Thud] - Ow!
ow! 你想让她整夜都灌龙舌兰吗?
Want her doing tequila shots all night? I'll be the one cleaning up the vomit.
到时候还不是我来清理呕吐物
Besides, I touched a heart today, Porny.
另外,我今天碰了心脏...
毛片小女王
[Doorbell]
大部分时候,疼痛可以控制.
[Meredith] Most of the time, pain can be managed.
再给我倒一杯
Pour me another one.
但是有时候,疼痛在你 最不期待的时候出现...
But sometimes, the pain gets you when you least expect it.
我在告诉你呢,任何时候.
I'm telling you. Any second.
疼痛来的不择手段而且无法停止.
Hits way below the belt and doesn't let up.
我到处找你.
I have been looking... everywhere for you.
Well...
那...你现在找到我了.
- You found me. - So...
所以...
you going to sign those divorce papers or not?
你会在离婚协议书上签字,还是不会?
疼痛--
Pain. You just have to fight through.
你只需要奋力与之搏斗
Because the truth is you can't outrun it.
因为事实是,你没办法逃脱, 而且生活只会制造更多的疼痛
And life always makes more.
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译:Parry Wong (澳洲) 校对:Parry Wong (澳洲)
Grey's Anatomy S205 风软论坛 荣誉出品 www.1000fr.com